Vitality versus GamerLegion
Vitality 对阵 GamerLegion
It's the best versus the brave.
这是强者对勇者。
Because the challenge at hand tonight for GamerLegion
因为今晚摆在 GamerLegion 面前的挑战
feels insurmountable
看起来几乎无法逾越
from every single angle.
从任何角度看都太难了。
And that is exactly why we'll cheer.
但也正因如此，我们才会为他们喝彩。
Fort Worth.
沃斯堡。
It's time to witness greatness, either via Vitality
现在就是见证伟大的时刻，要么是 Vitality
or the upset
要么就是一场
of the year.
年度级别的冷门。
Let's get into it.
比赛开始吧。
As Connor just said,
正如 Connor 刚才所说，
potentially, this would have to be the upset of the year.
这很可能会成为今年最大的冷门。
Something we would never expect
这是我们完全想不到这套阵容能打出来的内容。
They're not here to waste time,
他们上来就不打算浪费时间，
and neither are Vitality.
而 Vitality 这边也一样。
A couple of headshots quickly,
上来就是两个爆头，
gets that opening,
直接拿到首杀，
but suddenly everybody's gone.
结果转眼间人就全倒了。
Wiped off the board.
被直接清空。
are GamerLegion, and this is a perfect hold.
这波防守，堪称完美。
A simple strategy that gets shut down.
一个简单的战术就这样被掐灭了。
The B play, and the B site is closed.
这波打 B，B 包点被彻底封死。